http://www.fischbein.com/privacy-policy/

The Duravant family of operating companies serve the food processing, packaging and material handling segments.
CUSTOMER SERVICE +32 2 555 11 70 from MONDAY to FRIDAY (8am to 5pm)
Search
Search for:
English
Nederlands (Dutch)
Privacy policy
At FISCHBEIN we value privacy and transparency, so we wanted to let you know that our company complies with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) that has entered in force on May 25th 2018.
We want you to know what personal data we collect and what we do – and don’t do – with it.
What kind of data we collect
FISCHBEIN is only interested in personal data that helps ttus deliver relevant materials and product offerings to you. In our customer & vendor database we have only the following personal information you have freely given us:
-Name & Title
– e-mail address
– Postal address of your Company
– Professional phone number
-Business name and size
-Industry type
What we do with data we collect
We use your personal data to first and foremost ensure you receive the information you have requested. We also use it to make sure you receive important product information, service bulletins, updates, promotions, surveys and superior customer service.
What we do not do with data
We do not share personal information outside our company. FISCHBEIN has never and will never sell your information to other vendors.
What’s next?
You can correct, amend or delete any of the information we have on file by contacting our Customer Service Team or email your request to: data.protection@duravant.com
Be assured that FISCHBEIN is committed to protecting the privacy of information and personal data
Sincerely,
FISCHBEIN
Fischbein international
Paepsem Business Park Boulevard Paepsem 8 B1070 Brussels, Belgium
About WordPressWordPress.orgDocumentationSupportFeedbackSearch
